Guide to the Fedor Stepun Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs and Artwork, 1902-65; Series VI; 0.4; (1 box)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS
    - Others: including Bishop Anastasii, Hermann von Beckerath, Andrei Bely, Fr. Benigson, N. Berdiaev, T. and O. Dukhovskaia, A. Fondaminskii, Marta Fuchs (signed), Fr. Gizetti, S. I. Hessen, M. F. Ignatiuk-Lenin, V. Ivanov, Richard and Alice Kroner (with letter), Hans Ledejewski (signed), Carl Muth, Prince A. Obolenskii, Alexander Schmemann, Willi Schmidt, O. A. Shor, L. A. Tarasevich, Paul Tillich (with notes by Tillich), D. Tschizewskij (signed), Boris Zaitsev, V. V. Zen'kovskii, 1905-48, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 2200)
    - Buildings and unidentified persons, 1915, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 2201)
    - Photographs of artwork, including portraits and busts of FAS, A. Stepun (first wife, nee Serebrennikova), and N. Stepun. Portraits by Kate Morell- Krahmer and unidentified artists, 1937-51, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 2202)
      Includes letter from unidentified artist
  - ARTWORK
    - "Die Zodiakale Symbolier van het Evangelie naar Markus": holograph astrological chart, bound, 1959 Sep
      See: Oversize, Box 71, folder 2205
    - Sketch of FAS: pen and ink, by Sergei Ivanov, 1964
      See: Oversize, Box 71, folder 2206
    - Poster for FAS's lecture "Theater und Film als Ausdruck zweier Weltanschauungen": (2 c.), 1946 Nov 24
      See: Oversize, Box 71, folder 2207
- Oversize, 2; (1 box)
  Oversize contains oversize material from Series IV and Series VI, arranged in series order.
  - SERIES IV. PERSONAL PAPERS
    - Identification Papers and Official Documents
      - Honorary degree from Universität Heidelberg, and copy, 1960 Feb 7 (Box 71, Folder 2203)
  - SERIES VI. PHOTOGRAPHS AND ARTWORK
    - Photographs
      - Photographs of FAS, studio portraits, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 2204)
    - Artwork
      - "Die Zodiakale Symbolier van het Evangelie naar Markus": holograph astrological chart, bound, 1959 Sep (Box 71, Folder 2205)
      - Sketch of FAS: pen and ink, by Sergei Ivanov, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 2206)
      - Poster for FAS's lecture "Theater und Film als Ausdruck zweier Weltanschauungen": (2 c.), 1946 Nov 24 (Box 71, Folder 2207)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 4; (2 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 42 folders 1387, 1394, 1399 (Box 72, Folder 2208-2211)
  - Box 45 folders 1440, 1441, 1443, 1446 (Box 72, Folder 2212)
  - Box 46 folders 1450, 1452, 1455 (Box 72, Folder 2213)
  - Box 48 folders 1469, 1472, 1474 (Box 72, Folder 2214)
  - Boxes 50-54 folders 1531, 1561, 1562, 1596, 1605, 1609, 1622, 1623, 1642, 1651, 1665, 1676 (Box 73, Folder 2215)
  - Boxes 55-57 folders 1685, 1700, 1714, 1727, 1728, 1757, 1763, 1768, 1772 (Box 73, Folder 2216)
  - Box 66-67 folder 1979, 1980, 2074 (Box 73, Folder 2217)
  - Box 68-69 folders 2122, 2146, 2151, 2152, 2153 (Box 73, Folder 2218-2219)